Contact

+6285814226758 (Mobile) m.fuadiy@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/muhammadfuadiy (LinkedIn) github.com/mfuadiy (Portfolio)

Top Skills

React Native

PHP

Database Administration

Languages

Bahasa Indonesia (Native or Bilingual)

Bahasa Inggris (Professional Working)

Certifications

Manajemen Resiko Dana Pensiun Filing System
Junior Digital Artist

Muhammad Fuadiy

System Analyst at DPK BPJS Ketenagakerjaan

Jakarta, Indonesia

Summary

A Systems Analyst with over 3 years of experience leading projects, analyzing, designing, developing, and testing systems within a financial company. Highly proficient in web-based application development. Eagerly seeking new experiences outside of the financial sector.

Experience

DPK BPJS Ketenagakerjaan

System Analyst

February 2020 - Present (3 years 11 months)

Greater Jakarta Area, Indonesia

- 1. Analyzed and designed business processes.
- 2. Analyzed any potential IT products/applications to fit current needs.
- 3. Analyzed, designed, and developed desktop and mobile-based applications.
- 4. Analyzed, designed, developed, and maintained IT infrastructure.
- 5. Led SIT, UAT, and user trainings.
- 6. Documented IT system and IT infrastructure needs.

Performed troubleshooting on computer devices.

PT. Sunindo Kookmin Best Finance

Software Developer

July 2019 - January 2020 (7 months)

Greater Jakarta Area, Indonesia

- 1. Developed the IT system based on user requests using Java, JavaScript, and IBM DB2.
- 2. Analyzed and tested features before their deployment.
- 3. Ensured that the IT system and IT infrastructure are running smoothly.
- 4. Documented IT system and IT infrastructure needs.
- 5. Established regulations related to computerization.

SCM Asia Sdn Bhd

Video Editor

May 2018 - August 2018 (4 months)

Education

Politeknik Negeri Jakarta (PNJ)

Bachelor's degree, Teknik Informatika konsentrasi Teknik Multimedia dan Jaringan · (2014 - 2018)

Asia e University

Bachelor's degree, Information and Communication

Technology · (2014 - 2018)